Finding Aid to the Heather Allore Papers, 1993-1998
Allore, Heather papers, 1993-1998
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Heather Allore Papers, 1993-1998
7654
Heather G. (Heather Gwynn) Allore, 1961-
.4 cubic ft.
Agendas, notes, documents, and correspondence
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Agendas, notes, related documents, and correspondence from meetings of a Cornell University Working Group on Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Issues,1993-1995, and of the Advisory Board to Cornell's Lesbian, Gay, and Bisexual Resource Office, 1995-1998. Also, notes and correspondence from the Cornell Lesbian/Bisexual/Gay Alliance in 1993.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Allore was a graduate student at Cornell University, then a post-doctorate fellow, and worked to improve the campus climate around lesbian, gay, and transgender issues.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Agendas, notes, related documents, and correspondence from meetings of a Cornell University Working Group on Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Issues, Sept. 1993-1995, and of the Advisory Board to Cornell's Lesbian, Gay, and Bisexual Resource Office, 1995-1998. Carlisle Douglas was Coordinator of the Resource Office during this time. Also, notes and correspondence from the Cornell Lesbian/Bisexual/Gay Alliance in 1993. The Alliance was a short-lived group of staff, faculty, and students who met to encourage the University to take action to address lesbian/gay/bisexual issues on campus.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Names
Douglas, Carlisle.; Cornell University. Lesbian, Gay, and Bisexual Resource Office. Advisory Board.; Cornell University. Working Group on Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Issues.; Alliance (Cornell University).; Cornell University--Societies, etc.
Subjects
Gays--Political activity--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Lesbians--Political activity--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Bisexuals--Political activity--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Douglas, Carlisle.; Cornell University. Lesbian, Gay, and Bisexual Resource Office. Advisory Board.; Cornell University. Working Group on Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Issues.; Alliance (Cornell University).; Cornell University--Societies, etc.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIAL
Alliance Records, collection # 37-7-2755
Container List
- Working Group on GLB Issues, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- LGBROAG applications and membership, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- LGBROAG (LGBROAB): Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual Resource Office Advising Group/Board, 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- LGBRO Mission Statements and Planning Documents, 1994-1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Search for Coordinator of LGBRO, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Search for Coordinator of LGBT Peer Counseling Service, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- LGBRO (LGBTRC) Reports and Statistics, 1994-1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Domestic Partnerships/Benefits/Work and Family Life (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Materials: Publicity, Resources, Events (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Correspondence and memos, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Graduate and Professional Student Assembly, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Cornell LGBT related publicity/print materials (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Non-Cornell-related print materials (Box 2, Folder 2)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Publications Removed From Collection 7654:
OH... Victoria, B.C., Canada, No. 5, Nov. 1993.
Progress Toward Diversity: Annual Report on the Status of Women, American Indians, Asian Americans, Black Americans, and Hispanic Americans. Cornell University, May 1993.